♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 23=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 23 =
You want to marry Fu Sihan.
تريد الزواج من فو سيهان.
So I took you into the family,
لذلك أخذتك إلى العائلة ،
and handed you the opportunity.
وأعطاك الفرصة.
But you messed it up yourself.
لكنك أفسدت الأمر بنفسك.
Now you came to me again.
الآن جئت إلي مرة أخرى.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Fu Rong.
فو رونغ.
Don't treat me like I'm stupid.
لا تعاملني كأنني غبي.
I was reported on going to the Obstetrics.
تم الإبلاغ عن ذهابي إلى طب التوليد.
My agent had already kept things down.
وكيل أعمالي قد أبقى الأمور بالفعل.
It was you who got those reports published again.
أنت الذي نشرت هذه التقارير مرة أخرى.
But you still worked with me after knowing that.
لكنك ما زلت تعمل معي بعد معرفة ذلك.
You just want to use me to get rid of Yun Xiangxiang.
أنت فقط تريد استخدامي للتخلص من يون شيانغشيانغ.
So you can marry him.
لذلك يمكنك الزواج منه.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Fu Rong.
فو رونغ.
You are just an adopted daughter.
أنت مجرد ابنة بالتبني.
Sihan is the future Chairman.
سيهان هو رئيس المستقبل.
And I want to be
وأريد أن أكون
the real
الحقيقي
Chairman's wife.
زوجة الرئيس.
Fu Rong, you just wait.
فو رونغ ، أنت فقط انتظر.
I'm not done with you.
أنا لم أنتهي معك.
Who does she think she is?
الذي قالت انها لا اعتقد انها؟
Wow!
رائع!
River snails rice noodles, stinky tofu,
نودلز الأرز الحلزوني ، التوفو النتن ،
and durian layer cake.
وكعكة طبقة دوريان.
I'm the happiest person in the world!
انا اسعد انسان في العالم!
There are all for you.
هناك كل شيء من أجلك.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
There are eight rules you need to obey while living with me.
هناك ثماني قواعد يجب أن تلتزم بها وأنت تعيش معي.
You have to go along with my eating habits.
عليك أن تتماشى مع عاداتي في الأكل.
You can't eat anything I don't like.
لا يمكنك أن تأكل أي شيء لا أحبه.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
there's only one rule.
ق هناك قاعدة واحدة فقط.
Whatever you like,
ايا كان ما تحب
that is the rule.
هذه هي القاعدة.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Oh, Fu Sihan.
أوه ، فو سيهان.
I've always wanted to ask you this.
لطالما أردت أن أسألك هذا.
Call me Han.
اتصل بي هان.
Just like in your comic.
تماما كما هو الحال في فكاهي الخاص بك.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
I really can't.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع.
Han.
هو.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I didn't hear you.
لم اسمعك.
Han.
هو.
OK?
نعم؟
Yes.
نعم.
Ask away.
نسأل بعيدا.
I want to ask
اريد أن أسأل
what happened to your legs?
ماذا حدث لرجليك؟
My legs.
ساقاي.
They got injured in the car crash seven years ago.
لقد أصيبوا في حادث سيارة قبل سبع سنوات.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Even your father...
حتى والدك ...
I've been thinking.
كنت افكر.
If I didn't
إذا لم أفعل
ask my father to take me on the trip,
اطلب من والدي اصطحابي في الرحلة ،
he wouldn't have died.
لم يمت.
I know I'm difficult to be with.
أعلم أنه من الصعب أن أكون مع.
But everything I do
لكن كل ما أفعله
is to protect myself.
هو حماية نفسي.
It's okay.
حسنا.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
I'll be the one to protect you.
سأكون الشخص الذي يحميك.
There's news from the United States.
هناك أخبار من الولايات المتحدة.
Yes.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
Mr. Fu.
السيد فو.
Just like I thought.
تماما كما اعتقدت.
That car crash
أن تحطم السيارة
wasn't an accident at all.
لم يكن حادثا على الإطلاق.
It was her?
كانت هي؟
So we...
لذلك نحن ...
I lived under disguise for so long
عشت متخفيا لفترة طويلة
just for today.
فقط لليوم.
He said he'll hand me the evidence in person.
قال إنه سوف يسلمني الدليل شخصيًا.
Buy a ticket for me.
شراء تذكرة لي.
I'm going to the United States.
انا ذاهب الى الولايات المتحدة.
Should we tell Miss Yun
هل يجب أن نخبر الآنسة يون
about your legs?
حول ساقيك؟
No.
رقم.
The more she knows,
كلما عرفت أكثر ،
the more dangerous it is for her.
كلما كان الأمر أكثر خطورة عليها.
That's a risk
هذا خطر
I cannot take.
لا يمكنني أن آخذ.
You sleep like a little piggy,
أنت تنام مثل الخنزير الصغير ،
just like yesterday.
تماما مثل البارحة.
You don't even know when you get carried to the bed.
أنت لا تعرف حتى متى يتم نقلك إلى السرير.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
All the dreams you had in your comic,
كل الأحلام التي حلمت بها في رسالتك الهزلية ،
I'll realize them for you one by one.
سأدركهم لك واحدًا تلو الآخر.